防患于未然
Brace the wind.
陛下 光之王已完全兑现承诺
The Lord of Light has made good on his promise, my king.
他的火焰消融了积雪
His fires have melted the snows away.
前路畅通
The way ahead is clear.
进军临冬城
We ride for Winterfell.
你定能马到功成
And you will take it.
主让我看到波顿之旗在烈焰中燃烧
The Lord has shown me Bolton banners burning.
你会得到你合法的王位
You will receive what is yours by right.
陛下
Your Grace.
准备整队进军
Prepare to form up.
陛下
Your Grace.
讲
Tell me.
大批士兵 在黎明前叛逃
The men, many deserted before dawn.
逃了多少
How many?
将近半数
Nearly half.
所有佣兵也把战马都骑走了
All the sellswords with all the horses.
陛下
Your Grace.
有话直说 还有什么能糟过叛逃
Speak up. Can't be worse than mutiny.
放她下来
Cut her down.
陛下
Your Grace.
刚刚梅丽珊卓夫人也逃离军营了
The Lady Melisandre was just seen riding out of camp.
召集剩余人马列队
Get the men into marching formation.
进军临冬城
On to Winterfell.
只见他举高双手
He raised his hands
所有死人就立刻站起身来
and they all stood up at once.
数以万计 简直是这世上最强大的军队
Tens of thousands of them. The biggest army in the world.
你打算怎么对付他们
So what are you gonna do?
只能希望他们不会爬城墙
I'm gonna hope they don't learn how to climb the Wall.
但那些龙晶...
But the dragonglass...
没人拿得回来了
No one's ever getting that back now.
再说作用也不大
It wouldn't have mattered anyway.
除非我们有一大堆
Not unless we had a mountain of it.
可你杀了一个异鬼啊
But you killed a white walker.
用长爪剑
With Longclaw.
他们击碎钢斧 就像击碎玻璃一般
I saw them shatter steel axes like they were glass.
-但那长爪剑   -是瓦雷利亚钢
- But Longclaw... - Is Valyrian steel.
七大国内现存几把瓦雷利亚钢剑
How many Valyrian steel swords are left in the Seven Kingdoms?
屈指可数
Not enough.
我是史上第一任
The first Lord Commander in history
为挽救野人性命
to sacrifice the lives of sworn brothers
而牺牲了守夜人兄弟的总司令
to save the lives of wildlings.
跟黑城堡里最招恨的人交友
How's it feel to be friends
感觉如何
with the most hated man in Castle Black?
从我第一天来此 你就是我朋友
You were friends with me when I first came here.
我那时可没机会赢得什么选举
And I wasn't winning any elections back then.
敬我俩一杯
Here's to us, then.
随他们挖苦去吧
Long may they sneer.
怎么了
What?
我想求你件事
I wanted to ask you something.
只能向你求助
To ask something of you.
把我 吉莉和孩子派去旧镇
Send me, Gilly, and the baby to Oldtown
这样我就有机会成为学士
so I can become a maester.
那才是我的志向所在 而不是当战士
That's what I'm meant to be. Not this.
山姆 你得留下
I need you here, Sam.
如果你走了 谁还能为我提供可靠建议
If you leave, who's left to give me advice I trust?
不是还有艾德吗
Well, there's Edd.
我当上学士的话 会对你更有帮助
I'd be more use to you as a maester.
因为伊蒙学士不在了 我会比任何人都更有用
More use to everyone now that Maester Aemon is gone.
学城有世上最大的图书馆
The Citadel has the world's greatest library.
我会学到很多历史 谋略 医术
I'll learn about history, strategy, healing.
还有其他知识
And other things,
能在异鬼来袭时派得上用场
things that will help when-- when they come.
要是吉莉还得留下来 她会没命的
If Gilly stays here, then she'll die.
被她起名叫山姆的那孩子也会没命
And the baby that she named after me will die.
最后为了保护他们 我也会搭上性命
And I'll end up dying, too, trying to protect them.
如此一来 我临死前看到的最后一幕
Which means that the last thing that I'll see in this world
将是他们被我辜负之后失落的眼神
will be the look in her eyes when I fail them.
我宁愿直面万千异鬼 也不愿如此
And I'd rather see a thousand white walkers than see that.
谢谢你
Thank you.
到了学城 他们还是会逼你立誓戒色的
You know that the Citadel will make you swear off women, too.
有种他们试试看
Oh, they'll bloody try.
-山姆  -怎么了
- Sam. - What?
山姆
Sam.
你刚被人打得半死 你是怎么...
You had just been beaten half to death. How did you--
我很小心的
Oh, very carefully.
很高兴世界末日还能给某人带来点好处
I'm glad the end of the world's working out well for someone.
我会回来的
I'll come back.
祝你早日归来
To your return.
祝我早日归来
To my return.
嘿 这边
Aye, this way.
小姐
My lady!
史坦尼斯
Stannis.
史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩率领全部人马杀来了
Stannis Baratheon is coming. His whole army.
你怎么知道是史坦尼斯
How do you know it's Stannis?
他们举着烈焰红心旗
They're carrying his flaming heart banners.
我在黑水河之役见过 绝对忘不了的
From the Blackwater. I'll never forget it.
在这儿挖战壕
Trench here.
距城墙三百码的地方再挖一道
Another one 300 yards from the castle wall.
动作要快
Hurry them along.
-对了 克鲁  -在 陛下
- Right, Curlew. - Yes, sir.
在那两条斜坡间挖一道
Dig between those two rises.
-分散开  -我和你一起
- Spread out. - I'm with you.
-弓箭手!  -散开!
- Archers! - Spread out!
即刻派一队人征收粮草
And send out a foraging party immediately.
日出之时攻城
Siege begins at sunrise.
陛下 无法攻城了
There's not going to be a siege, Your Grace.
我们没法儿赢的
We've got no chance!
别杀我 求你了
No, please, please.
居然有女人为波顿出战
Bolton has women fighting for him?
我并不是为波顿家而战
I don't fight for the Boltons.
我是塔斯的布蕾妮
I'm Brienne of Tarth.
曾任蓝礼·拜拉席恩的御林铁卫
I was Kingsguard to Renly Baratheon.
他被跟你同样面孔的黑影杀死时 我在场
I was there when he was murdered by a shadow with your face.
是你用血魔法杀了他吗
You murdered him with blood magic?
是我
I did.
以拜拉席恩家族
In the name of Renly of House Baratheon,
蓝礼一世之名
First of His Name,
以安达尔人和先民之合法国王
rightful King of the Andals and the First Men,
七大王国统治者和全境守护之名
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms and Protector of the Realm,
我 塔斯的布蕾妮 判你死刑
I, Brienne of Tarth, sentence you to die.
有什么遗言吗
Do you have any last words?
尽你的职责 动手吧
Go on, do your duty.
看来任务完成了
Looks like we're done here.
我投降!
I surrender! I surrender!
我接受你的投降
And I accept your surrender.
我们回去吧
Let's head back.
我妻子肯定寂寞了
My wife must be lonely.
夫人
My lady.
我来护送你归寝
I've come to escort you back to your chamber.
请跟她走吧
Go with her, please.
我知道拉姆斯的为人
I know what Ramsay is.
知道他会怎么对付我
I know what he'll do to me.
如果我注定要死
If I'm going to die,
让我死得有尊严些吧
let it happen while there's still some of me left.
死
Die?
谁说你要死了
Who said anything about dying?
你不能死
You can't die.
你父亲是北境守护
Your father was Warden of the North.
拉姆斯需要你
Ramsay needs you.
不过他可不需要你的全部
Though I suppose he doesn't need all of you.
只需要能为他生育子嗣的部分
Just the parts he'll use to make his heir,
等你为他生养了一两个男孩之后 就没用了
until you've given him a boy or two and he's finished using them.
他就会找些骇人听闻的招数对付你
Then he's got incredible plans for those parts.
那我们要等他回来
So, shall we wait for him to come back
还是现在就开始呢
or should we begin now?
你让我决定
You're leaving it to me?
那好
Good.
现在开始吧
Let's begin.
臭佬... 住手!
Reek... stop!
住手!
Stop!
打开城门!
Open the gate!
他回来了
He's coming back.
看来我有事要做了
I can see I have my work cut out for me.
你俩滚出去
You two, out.
你在我名单上排第一 知道吗
You were the first person on my list, you know.
你可记得杀了西利欧·佛瑞尔吗
For killing Syrio Forel. Remember him?
记不清了
Probably not.
还有几个我要杀的人
I've gotten a few of the others.
千面神让我忘却很多
The Many-Faced God stole a few more from me.
幸亏他还把你留给我
But I'm glad he left me you.
知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
我听不清
I can't hear you.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
我是艾莉亚·史塔克
I'm Arya Stark.
你知道你是谁吗
Do you know who you are?
你是无名之辈
You're no one.
无足轻重
You're nothing.
女孩取走一条性命
A girl has taken a life.
不该取走的性命
The wrong life.
我说对了
I was right about her.
确实
You were.
你还没准备好
You're not ready.
完全没有
Not at all.
那人的命不该由你来取
That man's life was not yours to take.
女孩从千面神那里偷窃
A girl stole from the Many-Faced God.
如今她生有所欠
Now a debt is owed.
唯有死亡才能偿还
Only death can pay for life.
不要啊!
No! No!
不要 你... 你别死!
No, you... don't die! Don't die!
你为何哭泣
Why are you crying?
他是我朋友
He was my friend.
他不是 你不懂他说的话吗
No, he wasn't. Didn't you listen to him?
他是无名之辈
He was no one.
可如果你是...
But if you're...
那这是谁
who's this?
无名之辈而已
No one at all.
女孩从大厅取走人面之前
Just as a girl should have
也应该是无名之辈
been before she took a face from the hall.
人面为心无牵挂之人准备
The faces are for no one.
你依然心有牵挂
You are still someone.
对心有牵挂的人
And to someone,
人面堪比毒药
the faces are as good as poison.
我看不见了
I can't see.
怎么了
What's happening?
怎么回事
What's happening?!
-祝你归途平安  -谢谢
- I wish you a safe journey home. - Thank you.
原谅我 孩子
Forgive me, child.
愿你福星高照
I wish you all the happiness in the world.
说不定我会去探望你
Maybe I'll come visit you sometime.
说不定是我探望你呢
Maybe I'll come visit you.
早点来吧
Don't wait too long.
家里有个贵族千金等我去娶呢
Got a noblewoman to marry back home.
你想娶个贤良淑女
You want a good girl,
却需要个风骚浪女
but you need the bad pussy.
就等你了 爵士
Whenever you're ready, my lord.
这次别跟丢了
Try not to lose it this time.
我再也不让它离身
I'll never take it off again.
我知道你不想离开多恩
I know you didn't want to leave Dorne,
但我很高兴你要回家了
but I'm glad you're coming home.
你母亲对你万分牵挂
Your mother's desperate to see you.
我也高兴崔斯丹与我们同行
I'm glad Trystane is coming with us.
他是个好小伙
He seems like a nice boy.
你很幸运
You're lucky.
媒妁婚姻很少能...
Arranged marriages are rarely so...
如此美满
so well arranged.
你说母亲会喜欢他吗
Do you think Mother will like him?
只要看到你开心 她一定会喜欢的
If she sees you're happy, I'm sure she will.
你真的这么想吗
You really believe that?
除了自己的子女
Have you ever known your mother to like anyone
你见过母亲喜欢过别人吗
aside from her children?
她喜欢你
She likes you.
我可不确定
I'm not so sure about that.
听着...
Listen...
有件事我想告诉你
there's something I wanted to tell you.
也许我早该告诉你
Something I should have told you long ago.
所以...
So...
你现在已见过世面
now that you've seen more of the world,
也该明白世事多变
you've learned how complicated things can be,
人心险恶
people can be.
兰尼斯特家与马泰尔家曾是世仇
The Lannisters and the Martells have hated each other for years,
可你却爱上崔斯丹
but you've fallen in love with Trystane.
真有点意外 我是说 该有多巧
It was an accident, really. I mean, what were the chances?
你刚好爱上了
You happen to fall in love with the man
指定要嫁的人
you were assigned to marry?
其实...
My point is...
我们无法选择所爱的人
we don't choose whom we love.
只是...
It just, well...
我们情难自禁
it's beyond our control.
-是不是听起来很傻  -不 才不是
- I sound like an idiot. - No, you don't.
我只是想说... 我想说
What I'm trying to say... what I'm trying
却没能说出口的... 我知道你要说什么
and failing to say... I know what you're trying to say.
不 你不知道
No, I'm afraid you don't.
我知道
I do.
I know.
你和母亲的事
About you and Mother.
一直隐约知道
I think a part of me always knew.
我真的很高兴
And I'm glad.
为你是我父亲而高兴
I'm glad that you're my father.
弥塞菈
Myrcella?
弥赛菈
Myrcella? Myrcella?
你们爱她 对吧
You love her, don't you?
怎能不爱呢
How could you not?
当然你俩实在是希望渺茫
Of course it's hopeless for the both of you.
一个竞技场的佣兵 一个失宠的骑士
A sellsword from the fighting pits, a disgraced knight.
你们的身份都配不上女王
Neither one of you is fit consort for a queen.
我们却总是会爱上不该爱的女人
But we always want the wrong woman.
他总是这么聒噪吗
Does he always talk so much?
安达尔人乔拉
Jorah the Andal.
灰虫子
Torgo Nudho.
他不该在这儿
He should not be here.
是 可他确实在
No, but he is.
女王已下令将他逐出城去
Our queen ordered him exiled from city.
若不是因为他 女王已经死了
Our queen would be dead if not for him.
是真的 我差点也死掉 若不是因为这位...
小壮士
侏儒
应该是这个词
抱歉
我的瓦雷语鼻音有些重
有些涩
生涩 谢谢
Punela. Thank you.
很抱歉
I am sorry.
我没能在场为女王而战
Sorry I not there to fight for our queen.
你可真错过了一场好戏
You missed a good scrap.
那些都不重要了
None of that matters now.
我们在这儿戏谑得越久
The longer we sit here bantering,
丹妮莉丝在野外待的时间越长
The longer Daenerys is out there in the wilderness.
他说的没错 龙朝北飞了
He's right. The dragon headed north.
要找到她 我们就得往北走
If we're going to find her, that's where we'll have to go.
我们
We?
你是个兰尼斯特
You're a Lannister.
女王一心要把你们家族赶下王座
The queen intends to remove your family from power.
而我一心助她实现夙愿
And I intend to help her do it.
你到这儿才多久呢
You've been here for how many days now?
我已为她战斗多年
I've fought for her for years.
自她年幼时起
Since she was little more than a child.
-你背叛了她 -说话留神
- You betrayed her. - Careful now.
她放逐了你 两次 我记得
And she exiled you. Twice, I believe.
第二次拜你所赐
The second time thanks to you.
莫尔蒙 别把你的错怪到我头上
Don't blame me for your crimes, Mormont.
他说得对 女王放逐了乔拉
He's right. Our queen exiled Jorah.
他说的也没错 乔拉救了女王
And he's right. Jorah saved her life.
也许她的看法有变
Perhaps she feels differently about him now.
也许没有 只有去问她才能知道
Perhaps not. The only way we'll know is if we ask her.
好吧 让他加入我们吧
Fine, fine. I suppose he can join us.
只要他保证不趁我睡觉时杀了我
Just as long as he promises not to kill me in my sleep.
如果我要杀你 你可得时刻提防
If I ever kill you, your eyes will be wide open.
等等 我们凭什么要带上你
Forgive me, but why would we bring you?
什么意思
Pardon me?
你在野外捕过猎吗
Have you ever tracked animals in the wilderness?
没 但我有别的本事
Not precisely, but I have other skills that would be useful.
你很会打吗
Can you fight?
我以前打过
I have fought.
不敢自称伟大的战士
I don't claim to be a great warrior.
你骑术如何
Are you good on a horse?
还好
Middling.
你也就是会耍嘴皮
So mainly you talk.
还会喝酒 我至今还活着
And drink. I've survived so far.
我尊重你 但这次远征你帮不上忙
Which I respect, but you would not help us on this expedition.
不过你可以在弥林帮助我们
You would help us here in Meereen, though.
我们没人能够治理一座城市
None of us have experience governing a city
除了他
except for him.
你想向女王证明你的价值
You want to prove your value to the queen?
就在弥林这里证明吧
Prove it right here in Meereen.
他是个外国侏儒 不懂本地语
He's a foreign dwarf that barely speaks the language.
弥林人怎么会听他的
Why would the Meereenese listen to him?
他们不会听他的
They wouldn't.
但会听灰虫子的
They will listen to Grey Worm.
我要跟你们去
I'll come with you.
我会找到女王
I'll find our queen.
-你身体太弱不便走动  -我能走
- You are not strong enough to go anywhere. - I am.
他能 他是我见过的最有种的阉人
He is. He's the toughest man with no balls I ever met.
但你还是不能去
But you still can't go.
弥林人相信你
The people believe in you.
他们知道你代表女王
They know you speak for the queen.
是的
It's true.
只有无垢者能维护弥林稳定
Only the Unsullied can keep the peace in Meereen.
如果你走了 这个城市会发生内乱
If you leave, half this city will consume the other half.
还有弥桑黛
And Missandei.
女王最信任的人是弥桑黛
Our queen trusts no one more than Missandei.
而不是我
Certainly not me.
女王的闺中密友
The queen's closest confidante,
无垢者的指挥官
the commander of the Unsullied,
疤脸的外国侏儒
and a foreign dwarf with a scarred face.
祝你们好运 我的朋友
Good fortune, my friends.
弥林古老而辉煌
Meereen is ancient and glorious.
千万别把它毁了
Try not to ruin her.
好像就剩我俩了 安达尔人乔拉
Looks like it's you and me, Jorah the Andal.
去找几匹好马
Let's find some good horses.
我们有太多话要聊
We have so much to talk about.
你好 老朋友
Hello, old friend.
我以为我们相处得很愉快 你却弃我于不顾
I thought we were so happy together until you abandoned me.
你是怎么找到我的 这问题大概也没意义了
I suppose there's no point asking how you found me.
鸟鸣于西 鸟鸣于东
The birds sing in the west, the birds sing in the east,
只要你会侧耳倾听
if one knows how to listen.
它们说 你已另有用武之地
They tell me you've already found favor
辅佐龙母
with the Mother of Dragons.
她的确没处死我
Well, she didn't execute me,
这算是个好开始
so that's a promising start.
现在英雄们都离城去找她了
Now the heroes are off to find her
我却被困在这里
and I'm stuck here
还要安抚这座城市 避免内乱
trying to placate a city on the brink of civil war.
有什么像样的建议吗
Any advice for an old comrade?
情报最关键
Information is the key.
要清楚敌人的力量和战略
You need to learn your enemy's strengths and strategies.
要分清哪些是真盟友 哪些不是
You need to learn which of your friends are not your friends.
如果我认识一个消息灵通的人士该多好
If only I knew someone with a vast network of spies.
但愿如此
If only.
一个宏伟古城 掣肘于暴力 腐败和谎言
A grand old city choking on violence, corruption, and deceit.
谁会有能耐去驾驭
Who could possibly have any experience
这么个巨大又笨拙的野兽
managing such a massive, ungainly beast?
我确实怀念过你
I did miss you.
我知道
Oh, I know.
我们必须得回去
We have to go home.
可怜的小家伙
Oh, my poor, sweet thing.
是不是很疼
Does it hurt?
我们必须得回去
We have to go home.
卓耿
Drogon.
能带我回弥林吗
Can you take me back to Meereen?
你带我飞了多远？
How far did you carry me?
卓耿 我们得回去
Drogon, we need to return.
我的子民需要我
My people need me.
对了 没吃的了
Well, there's no food.
再怎么说 晚上你能搞点吃得来吧
At the very least, you could hunt us some supper.
认罪
Confess.
我有罪
I have sinned.
我承认
I see that now.
我许久以来怎能如此盲目
How can I have been so blind for so long?
我想重获清白
I want to be clean again.
望能免除罪责
I want absolution.
我梦到老妪高举圣灯
The Crone came to me with her lamp raised high.
在圣光照耀下...
And by its holy light--
想认罪吗
You wish to make a confession?
若我认罪 可否重获自由
Once I've confessed, will I be free?
那要看太后所犯何罪了
Your Grace will be dealt with according to her sins.
圣母仁慈为怀
The Mother have mercy, then.
我承认 我跟其他男人有婚外奸情
I lay with a man outside the bonds of marriage. I confess.
他叫什么
Name him.
蓝赛尔·兰尼斯特
Lancel Lannister.
你的堂弟 先王的侍从
Your cousin and the king's squire.
-我那时寂寞无助  -你是有夫之妇
- I was lonely and afraid. - You had a husband.
可我丈夫一门心思在外寻花问柳...
A husband off whoring every chance he--
你不能拿他的罪行为自己开脱
His sins do not pardon your own.
愿诸神宽恕我
May the gods forgive me.
还有别人吗
Other men?
没了
No.
真没了
No others?
没了
No.
欺骗诸神 罪不可恕
Speaking falsehoods before the gods is a great crime.
你可明白
You understand this?
明白
I do.
传言说你的三个孩子
There are those that say your children
并非劳勃国王亲骨肉
were not fathered by King Robert,
传言说他们是通奸乱伦所生的杂种
that they are bastards born of incest and adultery.
谎言
A lie.
定是史坦尼斯·拜拉席恩编造的谎言
A lie from the lips of Stannis Baratheon.
他图谋篡夺王位 却被其侄捷足先登
He wants the throne, but his brother's children stand in his way.
所以故意造谣说孩子非劳勃亲骨肉
So he claims they are not his brother's.
卑鄙无耻
That filth.
这种传言绝不可信
There is not one shred of truth to it.
我否认
I deny it.
很好
Good.
但这些指控所涉罪名严重
But these are terrible charges.
全国上下必须知道真相
And the realm must know the truth of them.
若太后的供词属实
If Your Grace has given honest testimony,
审判定能还你清白
your trial will prove your innocence.
审判 我已认罪
Trial? I have confessed.
只认了一项罪
To a single sin.
其余罪名你都否认了
Others you have denied.
审判自能辨别孰是孰非
Your trial will separate the truths from the falsehoods.
谨遵总主教的睿智决断
I bow to the wisdom of Your High Holiness.
可我能否恳求圣母
But if I might beg
对我略施仁慈呢
for just one drop of the Mother's mercy.
我已许久未见我儿子...
I haven't seen my son--
早已记不清有多久了
I don't know how long it's been.
请允许我见见他
I need to see him, please.
你已迈出皈依正道的第一步
You have taken the first step on the path back to righteousness.
有鉴于此
In light of this,
你可以返回红堡
I will permit you to return to the Red Keep.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢总主教
圣母仁慈
The Mother is merciful.
应该谢她
It is her you should thank.
那是 那是
I will. I will.
我发誓 会日夜向她祷告
I swear it, day and night.
很好
Good.
我可以走了吗
Am I free to go?
等赎罪执行后
After your atonement.
赎罪
My atonement?
一个罪人来到你们面前
A sinner comes before you.
兰尼斯特家族的瑟曦
Cersei of House Lannister.
国王托曼陛下的生母
Mother to His Grace King Tommen.
先王劳勃陛下的遗孀
Widow of His Grace King Robert.
她犯下欺骗与通奸之罪
She has committed the acts of falsehood and fornication.
她已认罪并祈求诸神宽恕
She has confessed her sins and begged for forgiveness.
为证明她有心悔过
To demonstrate her repentance,
她将抛开所有尊严 诡诈
she will cast aside all pride, all artifice,
把诸神创造她时的本貌
and present herself as the gods made her
展现给全城的善男信女
to you, the good people of the city.
她满怀谦卑而来
She comes before you with a solemn heart,
褪去所有的隐私
shorn of secrets,
在诸神和世人面前赤裸…
naked before the eyes of gods and men...
踏上赎罪之路
to make her walk of atonement.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
可耻
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
-骚逼!  -无耻
- Cunt! - Shame.
-罪人!  -婊子!
- Sinner! - Whore!
-无耻!  -婊子!
- Shame. - Whore!
无耻
Shame.
-婊子!  -无耻
- Whore! Whore! - Shame.
无耻
Shame.
婊子! 罪人!
Whore! Sinner!
-无耻  -贱货! 操你弟的!
- Shame. - Bitch! Brother fucker!
-婊子!  -无耻
- Whore! - Shame.
-滚吧!  -无耻
- Fuck off! - Shame.
无耻
Shame.
-向皇室的奶头致敬  -你个贱货!
- All hail the royal tits. - You're a bitch!
无耻
Shame.
-干她!  -婊子!
- Get her! - Whore!
-贱货!  -混蛋!
- Bitch! - Fucker!
-混蛋!  -你个贱货!
- Fucker! - You bitch!
-无耻  -骚逼!
- Shame. - Cunt!
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
-操你弟的!  -贱货!
- Brother fucker! - Bitch!
我玩过的屌只有太后的一半多
I've had half as many cocks as the queen.
-贱货!  -无耻
- Bitch! - Shame.
-无耻  -罪人! 婊子! 荡妇!
- Shame. - Sinner! Whore! Slut!
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
-婊子!  -婊子
- Whore! - Whore, whore.
我是兰尼斯特 给我吹箫啊!
I'm a Lannister. Suck me off!
-给我吹箫啊 你个贱货!  -退后!
- Suck me off, you bitch! - Back!
-婊子!  -无耻
- Whore! - Shame.
无耻
Shame.
妓女
Whore!
婊子 淫妇 娼妓
Whore! Whore! Whore!
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
-贱货! 贱货!  -无耻
- Bitch! Bitch! - Shame.
操你弟的!
Brother fucker!
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
-婊子!  -操你弟的!
- Whore! - Brother fucker!
-婊子!  -无耻
- Whore! - Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
-无耻  -混蛋!
- Shame. - Fucker!
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
无耻 无耻
Shame. Shame.
无耻
Shame.
陛下
Your Grace.
你回来了就好
It's good to have you back.
来
Come.
我们扶你进去
We'll take you inside.
我要看看你脚上的伤
I need to have a look at those feet.
我可否有幸介绍一位御林铁卫新成员
May I have the honor of presenting the newest member of the Kingsguard?
为了陛下 他已立下静默圣誓
If it please Your Grace, he has taken a holy vow of silence.
他发誓不再开口说话
He has sworn that he will not speak
直到陛下所有的仇敌被铲除
until all His Grace's enemies are dead
所有的恶徒被驱逐
and evil has been driven from the realm.
当初是谁救了你 史坦尼斯
Who came to your aid? Stannis.
如今他需要你
Now he needs you.
我们兵力太弱 难以扭转战局
We don't have enough men to make any difference.
野人加入则能改变形势
The wildlings will make a difference.
野人绝不会为史坦尼斯而战
The wildlings will never fight for Stannis.
-我早就跟他说过  -你救过他们的命啊
- I told him before. - You saved their bloody lives.
他们若想在七大国境内生存
If they're gonna live in the Seven Kingdoms,
靠长城保命 就得为这鬼地方而战
safe behind our Wall, they ought to fight for the damn place.
-这场战争不属于他们  -打开城门!
- It's not their fight. - Open the gates!
史坦尼斯呢
Stannis?
希琳 小公主呢
Shireen? The princess?
总司令
Lord Commander.
有个你带回来的野人
It's one of the wildlings you brought back.
他说认识你叔叔班扬
Says he knows your Uncle Benjen.
说他还活着
Says he's still alive.
你确定他说的是班扬
Are you sure he's talking about Benjen?
据他说是首席游骑兵
Said he was First Ranger.
还说知道去哪儿能找到他
Said he knows where to find him.
那人说上次满月时在艰难屯见过你叔叔
Man says he saw your uncle at Hardhome at the last full moon.
-说不定是撒谎  -有这可能
- Could be lying. - Could be.
有办法确定真假
There are ways to find out.
-他人呢  -在那儿
- Where is he? - Over there.
叛徒
为了守夜人
For the Watch.
奥利...
Olly...
为了守夜人
For the Watch.
~第五季终~
FIX铁王座的世界组倾情奉献